godandscience.org 2010-06-24

# Privacy Statement for Evidence for God from Science

## General Privacy Policies

_Evidence for God from Science_ does not release any kind of personal information collected from the website to any entity outside our organization. This information includes, but is not limited to e-mail addresses, correspondence, and site statistics. Writing to the ministry will not add your name, e-mail, or any other personal information to any list (including our own). You must specifically request to be added to any lists. Now here is the legal/technical stuff:

## About Us

This is a privacy policy for Evidence for God from Science. Our homepage on the Web is located at [ http://www.godandscience.org](http://www.godandscience.org/). The full text of our privacy policy is available on the Web at [ http://www.godandscience.org/privacy.html](http://www.godandscience.org/privacy.html). Users may go to [ http://www.godandscience.org/privacy.html](http://www.godandscience.org/privacy.html) for information on how to opt-in or opt-out of use of their information.

We invite you to contact us if you have questions about this policy. You may contact us by mail at the following address:

    Richard Deem
    c/o Reasons To Believe
    P.O. Box 5978
    Pasadena, CA 91117
    USA

You may contact us by e-mail by [clicking here](https://www.godandscience.org/formmail.html).

You may contact us by telephone at (626) 87-BIBLE.

## Dispute Resolution and Privacy Seals

We have the following privacy seals and/or dispute resolution mechanisms. If you think we have not followed our privacy policy in some way, they can help you resolve your concern.

  * **Disputes** : Errors or wrongful actions arising in connection with the privacy policy will be corrected by our organization.

## Additional Information

This policy is valid for 1 day from the time that it is loaded by a client.

## Data Collection

P3P policies declare the data they collect in groups (also referred to as "statements"). This policy contains 3 data groups. The data practices of each group will be explained separately.

* * *

## Group "Basic information"

We collect the following information:

  * Click-stream data
  * HTTP protocol elements
  * Search terms

This data will be used for the following purposes:

  * Completion and support of the current activity.
  * Web site and system administration.
  * Research and development.

This data will be used by ourselves and our agents.

The following explanation is provided for why this data is collected:

> Data collected from all Web users: access logs, and search strings (if entered).

* * *

## Group "Cookies"

We collect the following information:

  * HTTP cookies

This data will be used for the following purposes:

  * Completion and support of the current activity.
  * One-time tailoring.

This data will be used by ourselves and our agents.

The data in this group has been marked as non-identifiable. This means that there is no reasonable way for the site to identify the individual person this data was collected from.

The following explanation is provided for why this data is collected:

> Cookies are used to track visitors to our site, so we can better understand what portions of our site best serve you.

* * *

## Group "Mailing registration"

At the user's option, we will collect the following data:

  * Online contact information
  * Preference data

This data will be used for the following purposes:

  * Completion and support of the current activity.
  * Contacting visitors for marketing of services or products. The user must **opt-in** to this usage.

This data will be used by ourselves and our agents.

The following explanation is provided for why this data is collected:

> This information is collected so that we can send you valuable and useful information which is relevant to your needs and interests.

* * *

## Cookies

Cookies are a technology which can be used to provide you with tailored information from a Web site. A cookie is an element of data that a Web site can send to your browser, which may then store it on your system. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it.

Our site makes use of cookies. Cookies are used for the following purposes:

  * Completing the user's current activity
  * User targeting

* * *

## Compact Policy Summary

The compact policy which corresponds to this privacy policy is:

    CP="CAO DSP COR CURa ADMa DEVa TAIa CONi OUR IND ONL UNI COM NAV INT PRE"  

The following table explains the meaning of each field in the compact policy.

Compact Policy Field | Meaning  
---|---  
CP= | This is the compact policy header; it indicates that what follows is a P3P compact policy.  
CAO |  Access is available to contact and other information.   
DSP |  The policy contains at least one dispute-resolution mechanism.   
COR |  Violations of this policy will be corrected.   
CURa |  The data is used for completion of the current activity.   
ADMa |  The data is used for site administration.   
DEVa |  The data is used for research and development.   
TAIa |  The data is used for tailoring the site.   
CONi |  The data is used for contacting the user, if the user selects it.   
OUR |  The data is given to ourselves and our agents.   
IND |  The data will be kept indefinitely.   
ONL |  Online contact information is collected.   
UNI |  Unique identifiers are collected.   
COM |  Computer information is collected.   
NAV |  Navigation and clickstream data is collected.   
INT |  Interactive data is collected.   
PRE |  Preference information is collected.   
  
https://web.archive.org/web/20100624235033id_/http%3A//www.godandscience.org/privacy.html   
Last Modified July 17, 2009
